Name: Shafiq K. Elaradi Address: Bashir Saadawi St., Tripoli, Libya

Phone Number: +218 916416709 Email: shafiq.aradi@icloud.com

Personal statement

A highly motivated and organized software engineer with three-years and one month experience, my role is focusing on obtaining real world requirements, analyzing requirements, designing software, developing and testing software, and delivering the intended software, my goal is delivering high quality software that meets a client's requirements.

Technical Skills

- JavaScript
- C#
- Swift
- Java
- .Net Core
- Asp.Net Core
- Node.js
- HTML
- Vue.JsjQuery
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- SQL Server
- iOS Development

Work history

Software Developer – Alzheimer's Nurse app (October 2015 – June 2016)

Duties:

- Planning and controlling the project
- Gathering requirements and analyze them.
- Designing and developing an iOS application.
- Testing the application

Used Technology:

Swift

Software Developer – BSC Inner System (April 2017 – October 2018 / February 2019 – June 2019)

Duties:

Developing and designing the bureau's System

Used Technologies:

- Asp.net
- C#
- VB.Net
- SQL Server
- Oracle

Software Developer – Project NoCash (October 2017 – December 2017) Duties:

- Planning and controlling the project
- Developing and designing the app for both iOS and Android.

Used Technologies:

- Swift
- Java
- Firebase
- Node.js
- MongoDB

App URL:

• Android: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=ly.nocash.nocash

Software Developer – HNEC candidate and bureau backend System (January 2020 – March 2020)

Duties:

Developing and testing the election system.

Used Technologies:

- Node.js
- MongoDB

Software Developer – HNEC candidate and bureau backend System

(January 2020 - March 2020)

Duties:

Developing and testing the election system.

Used Technologies:

- Node.js
- MongoDB

Software Developer – Education System for The Ministry of The Education. (April 2020 – July 2020)

Duties:

Developing and designing The System.

Used Technologies:

- Asp.net Core
- C#
- Vue.Js
- SQL Server

Software Developer – HNEC OCVR System- Full Stack (September 2020 – Ongoing)

Duties:

Developing and testing the election system.

Used Technologies:

- C#
- Asp.net Core
- Vue.js
- SQL Server

Education

University of Tripoli (2010 - 2016) BSc in Software Engineering.

Languages

- Arabic (Native)
- English (Fluent)

Personal Interests

Astronomy, Technology, gadgets and Reading books.